upfront group
Here we go...it's up-cami. This time we have Rikako Sasaki of Angulum and
and Kisora Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory.
This program will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We will show you our recording, rehearsal, and other production processes.
First of all, let's take a look behind the scenes of the two MCs. I, Sasaki, was recently invited to perform at JAPAN JAM,
We were the first to perform as the top batter,
On that day, we heard our fans' voices for the first time in about 3 years,
When we stand on stage like that, we all wear ear monitors,
Even though we were wearing earphones, your voices were still reaching our ears,
It had been a long time since we last performed on stage, so I felt that we all had a lot of energy,
I think we will be allowed to speak out at regular live performances from now on,
I am sure that you will be allowed to speak out at regular concerts in the future, but this JAPAN JAPAN performance made me very happy and moved me a lot.
I was very happy and moved by the performance of JAPAN JAPAN. That's how I feel.
That was it, wasn't it? The last FES you are going to perform?
Yes. The last. Maybe. Last? It might be, but it's the last?
I heard that it was a festival, and I heard from the staff that it was very exciting because of that.
I think the fans who were able to attend the festival must have had a very precious and enjoyable time.
And just like Rikako, I, Numa, am really looking forward to seeing you again.
I was really moved to hear the fans' voices for the first time in a long time at the Taiwan event.
And after that, during the spring tour, we had a live concert without cheering, but even without cheering, the excitement was different, and it was really fun. I wonder what will happen to the calls for the singles released after the Corona Disaster,
I'm curious. I'm excited about that too.
I'm excited about that too, so I'm looking forward to it,
I'm also looking forward to hearing the calls of the new members for the first time,
I'm really looking forward to that too.
I know that I have a lot to look forward to in the future.
Let's start off with the newest member,
Beyonds Seek Fate Traveler Instrumental Recording
Here is the recording of the song "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler" by the Beyonds members from the latest single of Beyonds!
Try to get the words out as much as possible.
That's good.
Here you go, meme.
me
Me. - Me.
Okay, I'm going to go first, and then I'm going to go to the not-so-wordy one, too, Japan Trocker.
me me me
me
Just a little bit of plastic. Just a little bit of plastic wrapper.
Let's go a little bit on the edge.
Okay, just two plummy-parappers, please. Please give me two times.
Yes, really.
I've got a girl who's doing the "toot-toot-toot-toot" and a girl who's doing the "toot-toot-toot-toot".
And some of them are blowing their breath.
I've got one that's blowing his breath.
Which do you prefer?
I don't think they need to be too close together, but I'd prefer it if they're having fun with it.
So we'll do it the same way we're doing it now, and we won't take another one.
I'll take the one that's too low.
Maena-san! Excuse me! I'm sorry!
I can see you!
Wait! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Let's go again.
OK, the second half of the melody is different, so that's where we have to shoot. Let's start with the wordy one.
Here's the first one.
me
me me
me me me, Wali-chan, a little bouncy Wali-chan.
I'll just steal that part.
Okay, I'll just take the current take.
Okay, pattern one, that's it.
The other one's less wordy.
Let's try something a little more fun.
Let's try something like this. We-chan! Woe-chan!
Woe-chan!
Woe!
Woe! Woe! Woe! ♪
OK, we're done!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Let us seek our destiny
The kazoo rec is over!The kazoo rec is done!
Yay!!!
Subway has done kazoo before at Beyonce's, but this was our first time.
How was our first attempt?
It was fun!
It was so much fun, so difficult, so much fun! It was difficult!
It was difficult!
It was hard!
How was the subway?
How's the translation?
Translated.
It was kind of nostalgic, but...
You can do it!
It's normal.
You're really good!
You were really good! Listening to you...
I could hear the tone.
I felt a sense of fulfillment.
A sense of fulfillment.
I practiced a lot, though.
It's been a long time.
It's been 3 years, right? That's amazing.
It's been three years.
Really?
It's been a few years.
It's been a few years, but it's become a group that I've been associated with for a few years.
I didn't expect to see them here.
In the recording, there were two kinds of patterns, one was a normal sound pattern, and the other was a speaking pattern.
How was the subway? Do you talk?
It was the first time for me to speak.
I was always saying the melody, "True" all the time.
It was difficult.
It was hard to put it into words.
But I don't know,
It sounded like a human voice.
It sounded like vocal cords.
That's why it's easy to get on.
It's easy to listen to music,
I think it's easy to get on board when listening to music.
It makes you want to say something together with the music, that's for sure.
It was difficult.
It was difficult, because it sounded like my voice.
It was difficult to put music on it.
It was different from ordinary instruments or recorders.
Yes, that's right.
That is why I tried to play the kazoo, which is difficult to play.
I hope you will pay attention to the sound of the kazoo.
Please listen to it a lot and climb the mountain for the destiny of the original!
Yes, so KAZOO, that was amazing, I learned about the instrument called KAZOO for the first time.
What is this?
And everyone had a KAZOO in their own color!
I thought that the color of the Kazoo can be changed.
I also learned from this video that sounds and words can be separated,
I thought a kazoo was just a thing that made a similar sound,
I thought a kazoo was something that just booed out similar sounds, but it was the first time I saw that it could also carry words.
I was very curious about kazoo because I thought it was just a similar sound to a kazoo.
You know, it's very rare to have an instrumental part in a song, isn't it?
I also watched the music video with the two of us, and I really think it's a song that only beauty can do, and there are some problems in the song,
We thought about it.
I thought about it.
I didn't know what it was, but they answered it for me.
I really thought the whole song was enjoyable, so I hope you enjoy it.
I hope you will enjoy it.
Please pay attention to KAZOO.
Let's listen to it, everyone!
Please listen to it!
That's all for now.
Beyonds Seek me, traveller of destiny
Here is the KAZOO recording!
I hope you enjoyed it!
Next up is Juice Juice Risa Irie's Hair Arrangement... this time Risa Irie is doing hair arrangements for the Juice Juice members!
Let's see what kind of hair arrangement you can expect from Risa Irie, a member of Juice Juice.
I usually do various hair arrangements for the Juice Juice members as Irie Lisa's element, but today I'd like to show you how I do it.
Today I'd like to show you how I do it.
Today's guest is this person!
Hello!
Yay!
I'm Eva Tahikozaki from Juice=Juice!
Yes, so I've summoned Eva,
Today, I'd like to do a kind of hair style that even Eva's length can just barely do,Today I'd like to do a kind of a haircut that can be done just barely even with Eva's length,
I would like to do this haircut as soon as possible, as it is quite popular with people like you.
I would like to do it right away.
This hair arrangement was also requested by EvaTaxa-chan.
A hair style that is just barely doable even at my length, a bun!
I braided both of them together, and the final result is a bun like this,
This hairstyle is quite popular, isn't it?
Okay, I'll go ahead and do it.
First, I use a balm.
This is about right. If you take it on this side of the nail, it will go into the nail.
I recommend you to take it in this direction. The head of the nail here and the end of the nail here.
I'm going to focus on the head of the nail here and here. I'm going to put them all together with a focus on this area so that they don't come out.
The minimum you will need is two tiny elastics.
If you have a lot of candy pins, you can do it.
The parting of the hair is going to be a little bit jagged today.
It would be cute if it were straight, but the jagged parting gives the hair an eerie look, so...
I'm going to make it slightly jagged.
I'm going to fix it temporarily. Yes, I will. It's better to tie it up tight here so that the parting can be seen clearly.
You can tie it as you like, but the key is to tie it tight.
I see.
This is how it looks jagged.
Then, let's start braiding,
Today, I'm going to braid the back.
I think it's prettier on the back side because it shows the knit lines.
I think it's prettier.
I'll explain slowly to those who don't know how to braid.
I'm going to do it while explaining slowly to those who don't know how to braid.
I'm going to take a little bit of this and divide it into 3 equal parts.
First, divide into 3 equal parts.
The size of the braid is what you call it this time.
Bigger is better than smaller.
The less you take here, the more knots you'll have.
The less you take out here, the more hairs you'll have here.
But if you take a little bit more hair, the number of braids will be smaller.
I think this hairstyle is cuter that way.
Take the hairs at the ends and turn them back.
Take a hair at the end and turn it back.
Like that, we're going to braid it there.
I think it looks prettier if the knit is in the front than if it's knit in the back.
The key is to knit it forward as much as possible.
I see.
When you get to this point, all you have to do is knit backwards.
If I tried to do it like this by myself, it would be difficult to get the right feeling of how to do it backwards.
It's true that it's easier to do this haircut for someone else than it is for me.
It's easier to do it for someone else than to do it yourself.
You can't see the back by yourself unless you have a mirror.
It's a hairstyle that you can do by yourself.
I'm sure you can do it yourself, but maybe you can do it for your friend after watching this video.
It might be better suited for that kind of thing.
That's for sure.
Yes! Half and half done!
Like this.
Yes, back braid.
Oh, great!
Unravel just a little bit.
If you unravel it too much, it will come out as a pion,
So, I'm going to loosen it lightly, really lightly. I'm going to loosen it lightly, really lightly. I do it like this while explaining, but before a live performance, I do it in about 3 minutes. I always do it. I usually do the thinking work by myself once and try my best.
That's why I'm often asked to do it just before the show.
Uemura-san, Sakura-chan and I usually start working before the show.
That's a lot.
A lot. A lot.
Yes, a lot. This is what it looks like now.
This is the first time I saw it like this.
I'm going to put it together like this.
There is a way to make the pins more secure.
Normally, you would stick them in like this.
But if you insert one pin like this and then return it to this way
It's very secure even with just one pin.
The hair here is short.
And turn it over.
Wow! It's stable now.
Even with just one piece, it's fixed like this.
It's fixed so well.
The best way is to stop it so that the ends of the hair can be hidden in the braid.
I'm going to put pins in the braid.
It's like if you stick pins all over the place, it will be fixed.
But if you have long hair, it won't come out.
Hmmm.
But if it was Eva's hair length a while ago, I couldn't do this hairstyle, but now it's not so easy, you know, with Obu and such.
There's not a lot of variation in hair arrangement.There aren't many variations in hair arrangement.
Just by doing the former goddess, the atmosphere changes a lot, doesn't it?
I've already made a lot of hair clips.
I'd like to put on the hair clips.
Yes, point by point.
I'm going to fix them.
Here is here. I'm going to fasten them here. Here and there.
I'm going to fasten it up.
This hairstyle is not for daily life,
It's more for celebrations. It's for celebrations,
For example, entrance ceremony or wedding,
I think it's a very gorgeous and cute hairstyle for celebratory occasions.
It would also be cute with a big ribbon or something in the back.
I do that quite often.
Okay, it's done!
All right! It's done. Today, I'd like to show you a hairstyle that can be done even with shorter hair lengths.
The key points are to braid the back braid so that it looks like it's in the front, to make the parting a little zigzag, and to add a butterfly to make it more glamorous.
I also added some butterflies to make it more glamorous. It may be difficult to do alone, but I hope you will try it with your friends.
But please use this as a reference for your friends to try it. That's all for now.
This is Juice=Juice's EBATAKI Sato.
She's really good at it, very dexterous and amazing!
And they were so cute!
Both of them have
Their faces are great!
Nice hair.
Nice hands.
And I think a lot of people with hair this long have trouble arranging it, and the members had beautiful hair that could be used as a reference.
Hey, you know, Choucho was cute, too, and it suits her face. You know how she sticks the pins in?
I always ask Hirai Miyuki to arrange my hair at the concert. You can do it, Yuuki.
I've been asking her to do it for a long time, and she does it because she's so kind,
Yuuki does it that way, too.
I've experienced how stable it is, so I really want everyone to try it.
It doesn't fall off even if you do it for a day,
It's amazing. I thought Lisa-chan taught me a good lesson, so I would like you to refer to this video.
That's all about Lisa Irie's hair arrangement for Juice=Juice.
I am Megumi Yasuda. I am Mari Yaguchi.
So, we are going to have an event to celebrate the 25th anniversary of our debut, and the title is, Hello Project 25th Anniversary Morning Musume. 2nd Term, Mari Yasuzaki Yaguchi Presents 2.
The event will be held on May 26th in Tokyo, and it's getting closer and closer.
It's getting closer and closer.
What kind of event do you think it will be? Kay.
This time, you know...
Our debut single Morning Musume。 Summer Night Town
Summer Night Town's 25th anniversary event
and we're going to celebrate the 25th anniversary of the release of our debut single "Summer Night Town.
Hello Project's OG
Katsutarina
and current Hello! Project members will be coming to visit us.
Yes, that's right!
I think this will be a very precious collaboration.
You don't get to perform together very often, do you?
No, because this may be the last time we sing and dance with this lineup.
We're about 20 years apart, aren't we? Realistically.
That's right.
Of course we'll talk.
But this time, we're going to sing more.
We're going to have a lot of singing this time.
And there will be a guest!
Sayaka will be here!
Yay! Sayaka!
We are celebrating our 25th anniversary as 2nd term members.
Sayaka's decision was made recently.
We're in a bit of a rush.
A little bit.
But we'll be able to do a lot more.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Also, I'm very happy to be able to show you all three of us together,
I'm very happy to be able to show you the three of us together,
I hope all of you who have been supporting us for a long time will come to see the three of us together,
I hope that all of you who have been supporting us for a long time will be able to see the three of us together.
Please look forward to it.
Now then,
Today,
Today, I have invited one of the members who will be performing at the event.
This is Yumio Hira from the Beyons.
Now that Hirayu from the Beyons has joined us, how do you think the event is coming up?
Well, I don't know what's going on...
Well, I'm still nervous because I can't imagine what it will be like to be on the same stage with all the legends, but I'll do my best to make the event a great success! Wow! I'm so happy! You are so serious!
But you have great hobbies, don't you, Hirai-chan?
That's right.
Dancing, taking pictures, editing videos, etc.
Wow! That's amazing! You can do so many things!Oh! That's great! You can do so many things!
I heard that Hirai-chan's dance is one of the best!
Wow! I'm so proud of you! I'm a member of the Halo Pro Dance Club.
I have a favor to ask of you, Ms. Hirai-chan.
I have a favor to ask you.
We, Morning Musume。 Niki's debut single is called
It's called Summer Night Town.
I'd like to sing this song at the event.
You know the choreography for the interlude?
Yes.
We really couldn't do anything back then, and we were really scolded by our teachers.
We were really only able to spin around and step on the floor.
That's all we could do.
All we could do was just spinning and stepping.
So I'd like to ask Hiay-chan to choreograph the interlude of Summer Night Town, which is a little more powerful this time.
I'd like to ask you to choreograph the interlude of Summer Night Town.
Please do.
How about it?
How do you like it?
I'm very nervous, but I'll do my best.
I'm serious. Thank you very much.
I'm really saying, "I can't say no to this.
It's true.
If I could say no here, I'd have a strong heart.
I'm really sorry, but we're in our 40s, so...
Is it possible to be a little gentler?
Of course, I'd like to make a nice outfit.
I'm happy to hear that.
Do you have any suggestions?
What do you like? Well, what do you like?
One thing I'd like to ask is that since Sayaka will be a guest this time, I'd like the three of us to stand side by side.
I would like to have the three of us standing side by side, doing something together.
I'd like to have the three of us standing side by side together, and I'd like to have a sense that we are all doing it together.
I would really appreciate it if you could do it.
The current members are much better dancers than we are.
We dance with a sense of intimacy.
We've been told it's good.
I'm not that good at it.
So please take that into consideration.
I'm counting on you.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm glad.
Thank you, Hirayu.
Well, we'll have dance time on another day.
We'll start rehearsing together then, so please take care of it.
Thank you very much.
See you on that day!
See you later!
Thank you very much.
Well, please look forward to the day of the event to see how the choreography will be.
It's a very important event, so we're going to make it a spectacular one.
Yes, it's going to be a very rare event since we are already in our second season together.
Please come to this event!
Even if you're not a member of our fan club, you can still join us.
Even if you're not a fan club member, you can still participate.
I'm looking forward to seeing you there.
That's all for now, Megumi Yasuda
Mari Yaguchi and
Thank you very much.
Thanks to you, I can do my best.
Sasagiri Gokoto of Angulum
Kisora Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory
Next, here we go!
Tsubaki Factory Skip Skip Skip Vocal Recording
From Tsubaki Factory's latest single
Skip skip skip skip, please take a look at the vocal recording of Marin Fukuda!
Okay, let's start with the A melody of the first number!
Well, it's a little refreshing.
Not too flashy, but cool and fresh.
I'm trying to keep it cool and fresh.
I'm sorry for the suddenness, but I can see you today.
Heart fluttering sound
Basically, it's okay.
The notes are a little long.
I feel like I want to go a little tighter
Inviting water baby rain
After that, it's gonna rain black watermelon. After that, it's gonna stick out. After that...
Don't let them connect.
After this...
There's a star forecast.There's a star forecast.
I'll nuance it a bit here.
I'm sorry to drop in on you like this, but I'll see you today.
I'm sorry, I'll see you today.
It's like...
Okay, let's go to the B melody. I'm going to the west exit ticket gate if you don't notice and dance.
I'm on my way.
I guess this is it.
One, two, that's it.
And then we'll sing a little bit.
And the rest
Even the dust before the wall dances
I'll go a little harder there
Let's dance.
Put a little accent on that syncopated part
Taratatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatat
It makes it a little snappier.
Heart fluttering sound
Yes, sir.
Can I just take the first string one more time?
Can I get another hit on the first string?
Even the dust before the wind dances.
Let's try to get a little rhythm out of "Let the dust dance.
It's a party tune, so let's have a party.
That's a punch-in, that's a punch-in, that's a party tune, so let's party party party!
Let's do it.
I'm going to go get the ticket gates and hurry up.
I'm going to try a song I don't know. I'm going to try it.
I don't know this song, but I'm gonna get on it.
Tonight, I'm going for it, and it's my turn.
I'm gonna be totally skinny-dipping
Yoo wak, yoo wak, yoo wak, yoo wak
Ride on and on and on, romance
I can't even let go of my heartbeat, it's so badass
Skip, skip, skip, skip
Yeah, it's basically starting to sound good.
I wonder if I can get a little more rhythm out of it.
I wonder if I can get a little more rhythm out of the songs I don't know... like the song "Let's Try to Sing Along.
I don't know a song I don't know, maybe I'll try to sing along to it.
If you're just a little bit conscious of that, you'll be fine.
I think I can get a little more rhythm out of a song I don't know, like, maybe a song I don't know, maybe a song I don't know.
Hote-te
Hote-te-te... it's hard.
You should be a little more aware of that.
Yes, that's good.
Let's take two seconds out of the "heartbeat" volume.
I'm just saying, "To the beat of my own drum.
It's a little bit normal.
Just hold it till it beats.
It's hard to hold it until the heartbeat.
I'll make it start up a little faster
I'll make it a little faster on the uptake.
OK, then, the second A melody, yes
after the passing voice, use the brackets
I love you
I'll get a line, too.
A line?
Yeah.
"I love you. I love you.
I love you.
It's kind of camellia-esque.
I love you?
I love you.
See you.
Yes, ma'am.
What's this?
A boy says, "I love you," in a different voice.
And the boy says, "I love you," and I'm a little nervous.
That made me a little nervous.
And the girl says, "Oh, you're on tour?
So why is it that the boy is talking on his phone with his girlfriend, and the girl is talking on hers?
It's not a very heavy "I can love you" kind of conversation.
It's not a very heavy "I can love you" kind of thing.
You're saying this in a boy's context.
In a boy's setting.It's a boy's setting.
I see.
So it's kind of boyish.
Don't go too low. It's a little more casual.
I love you.
I love you. I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you.
You're good.
That's perfect.
I'm so embarrassed. Oh, my God, I'm so embarrassed.
Okay, we're done. Good job!
Thank you so much!
This song makes me skip just by listening to it.
It's such a cute song that makes you skip around just listening to it.
This time, it was Marin's recording video.
It was so cute! She was really cute!
They look so alike!
We were both saying how cute and adorable she was the whole time.
But even with all that, Marin's singing has gotten so much better, now that I'm listening to it up close.
I used to be the type of person who was scared of faces and seriousness.
I think that's why she's always so serious about recording now.
I used to be like that, but now I'm able to put on facial expressions.
You were doing hand gestures and it was so cute.
I added
"I love you, I love you, I love you..." and "Seduction.
and "Seduction".
It was so cute.
I love that you choreographed it.
It was very good. It was good.
Yes, Marin-chan, you have an aura that's getting stronger and stronger.
When we were performing together, I was already watching Tsubaki on stage.
I've been watching Tsubaki's stage with my own voice since then.
I was really impressed by Marin-chan's behavior, her civility, her performance, and her expression.
I was really impressed by your performance and your expression, which only Marin can do,
I am looking forward to seeing more of her in the future.
That's all for now. Skip! Skip! It was a vocal recording of Marin Fukuda. Angstrom's Limited Moment, Burn with Every Life
Lovable Human Life
On Sex
Angulum New Album
Pic Club
Now on sale
We love you for your hard work!
It's time to say goodbye to Upcami, the group that Rikako Sasaki and Kisora Hayashi have been working on for the past few weeks!
We've seen a lot of videos this time, but I thought the BEYONDS instrumental recording was really cool, and I'd like to share it with you.
I love the instrumental recording section at every Upokami.
It's great, isn't it? I understand.
I like to see professionals playing those instruments, but I thought it was quite rare to see the members playing them this time, so I really enjoyed it.
I was very happy to see Marin Fukuda's recording at the end of the show. I joined the group around the same time as Marin, about 2 years ago.
I wasn't that flabbergasted when I started working with Marin.
She would just go in and do whatever the director told her to do.
I thought I was more panicked,
I thought, "I really admire Marin-chan, who has a lot of guts.
Upokami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel as we will introduce you to parts of the artists that you normally don't get to see.
This time, upcami is joined by Rikako Sasaki of Angulum and
and Kisora Nounuma of Tsubaki Factory.
In the next episode, we'll take you behind the scenes of Beyoncé's rehearsal with the orchestra, the day of the performance, and the recording of Angelem's latest album
and the recording of Angelem's newest album "Big Love".
Enjoy!
I'm going to show you something.
Cool kids, cute kids...